CHASE TREADAWAY

UI DESIGNER



228-383-0641



Chase.uidesigns@gmail.com



Gulfport, Mississippi Remote/Relocation Ready

SUMMARY

Passionate UI Designer possessing creativity, ability to learn quickly, and time management skills as demonstrated by supervising 75 individuals while maintaining a 3.6 GPA. Seeking to leverage four years of case management and development experience to join an organization that values teamwork, structure, and their employee's ability to prosper.

EXPERIENCE

DEVELOPMENT COORDINATOR

New York, NY

Helpusadopt.org

Sep. 2020 - Feb. 2023

- Collaborated with Founder to secure fundraising over \$1.8 million USD annually for program.
- Creatively enhanced funding by 20% with team, resulting in \$200,000 increased revenue in 2022.
- Maintained and meticulously updated a dynamic database encompassing 20,000+ individuals, ensuring accuracy and precision for each entry.
- Managed fundraising mailings amounting to over 10,000+ individual letters sent yearly.

VOLUNTEER COORDINATOR CASA of Hancock County

Bay St. Louis, MS Aug. 2018 - Jan. 2020

- Provided dynamic training and supervision for over 24 CASA advocates and 35 children.
- Conducted 80 hours of national standardized training for volunteers per year.
- Drafted, proofed, and submitted legal documents to Hancock County Youth Court and participated in over 150 scheduled judicial hearings in a supervisory capacity.

PROJECTS

ROADRUNNER | RUNNER SHOPPING APP

Oct. 2023 - Present

UI Designer

• Designed high fidelity mockups for mobile application enabling runners to easily navigate, archive, and browse running gear.

LOCALFRESH | RECIPE WEB APP

Aug. - Sept. 2023

UI/UX Designer

- Conceptualized and designed web based responsive app by conducting User Interviews and User Testing.
- Synthesized user research to prototype high fidelity UI with mobile first design approach.

EDUCATION

CareerFoundry

Certificate in UI Design

Jan. 2023 - Jan. 2024

Tulane University of Louisiana

B.A. in Sociology

Aug. 2013- May 2017

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

User Interface Design

• 4 High Quality Projects

User Experience Fundamentals User Testing

- User Flow Analysis
- A/B Preference Testing

Prototype Design

• Rapid Prototyping

Wireframing

Front End Web Development

• Created Personal Portfolio Website

Leadership

• Supervised 75 individuals

Creative

• Enhanced funding by 200k

Empathy

• Social Science education

Organization

 Maintained 3.6 GPA with multiple commitments and jobs

TOOLS

Figma Canva
Adobe XD MS Office Suite
VS Code HTML, CSS, JS

Google Workspace Balsamiq Wireframes